okay so let's get into who actually runs the no kings protest no kings protests are organized by
the indivisible project which is ran by these two ezra levin and leah greenberg whom although
have criticized israel before ultimately still support the existence and maintenance of israel
as a state in a jewish state and have said and say things like hamas is a tea organization that
does not care about the deal of palestinians bombing civilians blah blah blah saying that
hamas celebrates the sacrifice of civilians as recruitment opportunities for their cause if we
could press a button to eliminate every hamas fighter i'd support it also framing what's going
on with israel as netanyahu's doing and not a product of the israeli society and israeli regime
again i'll write a blank check to netanyahu's government it's like this is literally the
easiest thing to find the people who are like oh where'd you get your information from where's your
source like oh i looked this up for 20 minutes and didn't find anything i don't know what google what
internet you're using but yeah if these are the people you trust to lead the no kings protest and
lead resistance people who are lockstep with establishment democrats zionists who support
the state of israel and cannot assign blame for what's going on in gaza and palestine to where
it actually needs to be which is the entire israeli government and israeli society and israel as a
keep going premises apartheid genocidal keep going i don't know what to tell you
it matters that protest has been co-opted by folks who see resistance and a resistance movement
as t-rists it matters that the same democrats who you have watched allow for this to get this far
are telling you that you should only engage in peaceful protest it matters that a woman who has
been linked to several mysterious deaths to a video involving child ritual sacrifice and the epstein
files is telling you that she supports the protests that you're involved in this matters because when
these are the aspects attached it tells you that you are being used and that what you are considering
to be protest is actually being weaponized against you to pacify you